{
  "doc_id": "1485837878-1761092975",
  "title": "1485837878-1761092975.pdf",
  "title_raw": "1485837878-1761092975.pdf",
  "text": "--- [Halaman 1] ---\n\nMEMORANDUM OF AGREEMENT BETWEEN FACULTY OF ECONOMICS UNIVERSITAS PENDIDIKAN GANESHA AND FACULTY OF ECONOMICS, ADMINISTRATION, AND BUSINESS STEFAN CEL MARE UNIVERSITY OF SUCEAVA No. 1946/UN48.13/KS/2025 FACULTY OF ECONOMICS UNIVERSITAS PENDIDIKAN GANESHA, Republic of Indonesia, represented by Prof. Dr. Gede Adi Yuniarta., S.E., Ak., M.Si., FACULTY OF ECONOMICS ADMINISTRATION, AND BUSINESS STEFAN CEL MARE UNIVERSITY OF SUCEAVA, Romania, represented by Professor Nastase Carmen Eugenia hereby agree to develop further collaborative relations between the two faculties as described herein. Area of Collaboration The area of collaboration includes such programs offered at and proposed by either institution and mutually agreed between the parties as feasible and contributory to the development of a collaborative relationship with mutual equality and reciprocity of benerfits. Methods of Collaboration The two parties agree to encourage and promote the following academic and scholarly activities: 1. Curriculum benchmarking, Joint Curriculum Development (planning learning outcomes, content and methods); 2. Visiting Professor and Guest Lecturer; 3. Providing training (upskilling and reskilling) for lecturers and instructors; 4. Student exchange programs (Bachelor's, Master's and Doctorate); 5. Joint research and/or joint scientific publications; 6. Community service; 7. Other activities as deemed approprite by mutual consent This cooperation agreement involves study programs and work units from the Faculty of Economics Universitas Pendidikan Ganesha. This Collaboration will be carried out by Accounting Study Program, Faculty of Economics Universitas Pendidikan Ganesha.From the Faculty of Economics, Administration and Business at Stefan cel Mare University of Suceava, similar bachelor's, master's and doctoral programs in the fields of: Accounting, Management, Business Administration, General Economics, Economics of Trade, Tourism and Services, International Affairs will be included. Faculty of Economics Universitas Pendidikan Ganesha and Faculty of Economics, Administration, and Business, Stefan cel Mare University of Suceava Romania agree to continues discussions on futher\n\n\n--- [Halaman 2] ---\n\ncollaborative activities as the oppurtunity arises. Both institutions recognize that collaborative efforts will be of mutual benefit and will contribute to an enduring institutional linkage for cooperation in education and research.All final aranggements involved in the implementation of Memorandum will be established in the development of the individual initiatives and will be mutually agreed upon by both institutions. This Memorandum of Agreement is valid for 4 (four years) with the understanding that it can be terminated by either party with three monthsÆ notice unless an earlier termination is mutually agreed upon. Revisions or modifications may be proposed at any times, effective from the date of written agreement signed by both parties. This Memorandum of Agreement becomes affective on the date of last signature. For and an behalf of Faculty of Economics Universitas Pendidikan Ganesha Republic of Indonesia Prof. Dr. Gede Adi Yuniarta, S.E., Ak., M.Si., Dean Date September 02, 2025 For and on behalf of Romania Dean Date September 02, 2025 Business Stefan cel Mare University of Suceava Prof. Nastase Carmen Eugenia Faculty of Economics, Administration, and",
  "total_pages": 2,
  "good_pages": 2,
  "garbage_pages_removed": 0,
  "metadata": {
    "page_id": "1485837878-1761092975.pdf",
    "url": "https://static1.undiksha.ac.id/arsip/2025/kearsipan/file-non-tte/1485837878-1761092975.pdf",
    "source_url": "https://static1.undiksha.ac.id/arsip/2025/kearsipan/file-non-tte/1485837878-1761092975.pdf",
    "target_site": "jdih.undiksha.ac.id",
    "content_type": "pdf",
    "last_updated": "Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:29:38 GMT",
    "parse_status": "parsed",
    "page_ids_included": [
      1,
      2
    ],
    "source": "jdih.undiksha.ac.id"
  }
}

---

{
  "doc_id": "511515287-1761092978",
  "title": "511515287",
  "title_raw": "511515287-1761092978.pdf",
  "text": "--- [Halaman 1] ---\n\nMEMORANDUM OF AGREEMENT BETWEEN FACULTY OF ECONOMICS UNIVERSITAS PENDIDIKAN GANESHA AND FACULTY OF ECONOMICS, ADMINISTRATION, AND BUSINESS STEFAN CEL MARE UNIVERSITY OF SUCEAVA No. 1950/UN48.13/KS/2025 FACULTY OF ECONOMICS UNIVERSITAS PENDIDIKAN GANESHA, Republic of Indonesia, represented by Prof. Dr. Gede Adi Yuniarta., S.E., Ak., M.Si., FACULTY OF ECONOMICS ADMINISTRATION, AND BUSINESS STEFAN CEL MARE UNIVERSITY OF SUCEAVA, Romania, represented by Professor Nastase Carmen Eugenia hereby agree to develop further collaborative relations between the two faculties as described herein. Area of Collaboration The area of collaboration includes such programs offered at and proposed by either institution and mutually agreed between the parties as feasible and contributory to the development of a collaborative relationship with mutual equality and reciprocity of benerfits. Methods of Collaboration The two parties agree to encourage and promote the following academic and scholarly activities: 1. Curriculum benchmarking, Joint Curriculum Development (planning learning outcomes, content and methods); 2. Visiting Professor and Guest Lecturer; 3. Providing training (upskilling and reskilling) for lecturers and instructors; 4. Student exchange programs (Bachelor's, Master's and Doctorate); 5. Joint research and/or joint scientific publications; 6. Community service; 7. Other activities as deemed approprite by mutual consent This cooperation agreement involves study programs and work units from the Faculty of Economics Universitas Pendidikan Ganesha. This Collaboration will be carried out by Applied Bachelor/Vocational of Public Sector Accounting, Faculty of Economics Universitas Pendidikan Ganesha.\n\n\n--- [Halaman 2] ---\n\nFrom the Faculty of Economics, Administration and Business at Stefan cel Mare University of Suceava, similar bachelor's, master's and doctoral programs in the fields of: Accounting, Management, Business Administration, General Economics, Economics of Trade, Tourism and Services, International Affairs will be included. Faculty of Economics Universitas Pendidikan Ganesha and Faculty of Economics, Administration, and Business, Stefan cel Mare University of Suceava Romania agree to continues discussions on futher collaborative activities as the oppurtunity arises. Both institutions recognize that collaborative efforts will be of mutual benefit and will contribute to an enduring institutional linkage for cooperation in education and research.All final aranggements involved in the implementation of Memorandum will be established in the development of the individual initiatives and will be mutually agreed upon by both institutions. This Memorandum of Agreement is valid for 4 (four years) with the understanding that it can be terminated by either party with three monthsÆ notice unless an earlier termination is mutually agreed upon. Revisions or modifications may be proposed at any times, effective from the date of written agreement signed by both parties. This Memorandum of Agreement becomes affective on the date of last signature. For and an behalf of Faculty of Economics Universitas Pendidikan Ganesha Republic of Indonesia Prof. Dr. Gede Adi Yuniarta, S.E., Ak., M.Si., Dean Date September 02, 2025 For and on behalf of Dean Date September 02, 2025 Faculty of Economics, Administration, and Business Stefan cel Mare University of Suceava Romania Prof. Nastase Carmen Eugenia",
  "total_pages": 2,
  "good_pages": 2,
  "garbage_pages_removed": 0,
  "metadata": {
    "page_id": "511515287-1761092978.pdf",
    "url": "https://static1.undiksha.ac.id/arsip/2025/kearsipan/file-non-tte/511515287-1761092978.pdf",
    "source_url": "https://static1.undiksha.ac.id/arsip/2025/kearsipan/file-non-tte/511515287-1761092978.pdf",
    "target_site": "jdih.undiksha.ac.id",
    "content_type": "pdf",
    "last_updated": "Wed, 22 Oct 2025 00:29:40 GMT",
    "parse_status": "parsed",
    "page_ids_included": [
      1,
      2
    ],
    "source": "jdih.undiksha.ac.id"
  }
}
